const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Tom Hanks was born on July 9th, 1956.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "My car ___ last night. ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was stolen", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "stole", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use passive voice when we don't know who did the action."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "The lion chased the zebra.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "My brother works at Amazon. He ___ weekly.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is paid", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "paid", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we prefer not to mention who or what does the action, because it's not known, it's obvious  or we don't want to say."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Shakespeare ___ Hamlet.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "wrote", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was written", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "He ____ in hospital.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "treated", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "is being treated", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when it is obvious who does the action, presumably 'doctors'."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Novak Djokovich ___ by Rafael Nadal on Roland-Garros.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was defeated", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "defeated", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we want to emphasize the receiver of the action."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Smoking ___ in this area.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is prohibited", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "prohibits", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice with rules and regulations."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "This house ___ by my father.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "built", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "was built", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "The passive voice is the correct answer in this question. When we want to say who does or what causes the action, we use by."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Passengers ___ to remain seated to avoid crowding.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "were asked", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "asked", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we are making general statements or announcements."
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Somebody has cleaned the window.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "Active voice ", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
  },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "It is a big company. It ___ five hundred people.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "employs", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "is employed", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the active voice when we say what the subject does."
    },
]

export default quiz1data